Welcome back!
欢迎回来！
You have been on quite the ride!
你经历了一段不平凡的旅程！
Not everyone gets this far.
并不是每个人都能走到这一步。
Let's continue your learning journey.
让我们继续你的学习之旅。
And see what else, you can learn.
看看你还能学到什么。
My name is Mary.
我叫玛丽。
I'll be your teacher for today.
我将是你今天的老师。
Today, in your Stoppr lesson, we're focusing on a new trap.
今天，在你的Stoppr课程中，我们将专注于一个新的陷阱。
Trap number 2.
陷阱二。
Skipping meals.
跳过正餐。
Yes.
是的。
It's not good to skip meals.
不吃饭不好。
For real.
真的。
Let me explain all this, very simply.
让我简单解释一下。
Skipping meals might seem harmless, buuuuut, it's not good.
不吃饭看起来没什么大不了的，但是，不好。
It can lead to big sugar cravings.
这会导致强烈的糖分渴望。
Let me tell you why.
让我告诉你为什么。
When you go too long without eating, your body becomes very hungry.
当你长时间不吃东西时，身体会变得非常饥饿。
To quickly get energy, your body starts craving sugary snacks or
为了快速获得能量，身体会开始渴望含糖零食或
sweets.
甜食。
Because it's a quick fix.
因为这是一个快速解决方案。
Your brain likes quick fixes.
你的大脑喜欢快速解决方案。
The craving mechanism is turned on.
渴望机制被激活了。
These quick fixes are bad for your body.
这些快速解决方案对你的身体有害。
This sugar give you a fast energy boost, but it's very short.
这种糖能给你快速的能量提升，但持续时间很短。
It doesn't last long at all.
它根本持续不了多久。
30 minutes later, you're feeling even more tired.
30分钟后，你感觉更加疲惫。
You're looking for more sugar to do a new boost, and a new boost,
你在寻找更多的糖来获得新的提升，再来一次新的提升，
and a new boost.
以及一个新的提升。
And boom, you're in the cycle.
然后砰，你进入了循环。
You're back in the drug.
你又回到了毒品中。
They got you, haha.
他们抓住你了，哈哈。
Your body is like a small child.
你的身体就像一个小孩。
You need to teach him that sugar is not the way.
你需要教他糖不是正确的选择。
The more you'll use healthy food for energy, the more sugar cravings
你越多地使用健康食物来获取能量，
will disapear.
糖的渴望就会越少。
Teach your child body how to behave.
教你的孩子身体如何表现。
Teach your child body what to eat.
教你的孩子身体吃什么。
Teach your child body when to
教会你的身体何时进食。
Step by step you are creating a routine.
你正在一步步建立一个习惯。
Eat healthy foods, at meal hours, in normal quantity.
在用餐时间吃健康的食物，保持正常的量。
The more your repeat, the easier it becomes.
重复得越多，就越容易。
The more your child body learns.
你的身体学得越多。
Don't skip a meal, don't eat sugary snacks.
不要跳过一餐，不要吃含糖零食。
It's like clockwork.
就像时钟一样。
At some point after 2 to 3 days, it will become obvious for you.
在2到3天后，你会发现这一点变得显而易见。
You wont even think about it.
你甚至不会去想它。
It will be very easy.
这将非常容易。
And your child body will just do everything in auto pilot.
你的孩子身体会自动完成一切。
And believe me, life in auto pilot is easy.
相信我，自动驾驶的生活很简单。
It's joyful.
这是快乐的。
You won't want to go back.
你不会想回去。
That's what I want for you.
这就是我想要给你的。
Easy days, easy weeks, in auto pilot, without sugar cravings.
轻松的日子，轻松的星期，自动驾驶，没有糖瘾。
This is your future.
这是你的未来。
I want you to think of your day as clockwork.
我希望你把你的一天想象成钟表运作。
If your clock is ticking right, you will never have to worry about
如果你的钟表正常运转，你永远不必担心
anything ever again.
再也不会。
Write your meal hours in your calendar if that makes you feel
如果这样让你感觉舒服的话，把你的用餐时间写在日历上。
comfortable.
舒服。
I hope you have a wonderful day.
希望你有美好的一天。
I will see you, in the next lesson.
我们下节课见。